RG 004:043, East Hartford Probate Court
Connecticut State Library
East Hartford Probate Court records
1887-1946
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Probate Court (East Hartford District)
50 cubic feet
Record books, none; Probate files, 1887-1946.
RG004_043
1997-009
Historical Note
East Hartford, Hartford County, Town established in October 1783, Parent Town: Hartford
The East Hartford Probate District was constituted May 1887, from the Hartford Probate District. The East Hartford Probate District serves the municipality of East Hartford.
Town of East Hartford, Probate District chronology:
October 1783 - May 1797, East Windsor District
May 1797 - May 1887, Hartford District
May 1887 - Present, East Hartford District
For Probate Court contact information and hours of operation see,.
Scope and Content
Record books, None. Contact the probate court to access original record books. See Alternative Form Available note below.
Probate files, 1887-1946. There is no index for these files.
Arrangement
Probate files are arranged in first by date, 1887-1933 and 1934-1946. Within each of these date ranges they are arranged alphabetically.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Probate records -- Connecticut -- East Hartford
Places:
East Hartford (Conn.)
Restrictions on Access
Researchers should first consult use copies when available. See Alternate Form Available Section below.
Probate files from 1921-1976 are RESTRICTED as they may contain confidential documents. Tax returns (succession, transfer and estate tax returns and all attachments) from January 1, 1921 and later are confidential per Connecticut General Statutes §12-15. Adoptions (all documents) from January 1, 1944 and later are confidential per Connecticut General Statutes §45a-754. Removals of parent as guardian of minor (all documents) and terminations of parental rights (all documents) from October 1, 1975 and later are confidential per Connecticut General Statutes §45a-754. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
Accession 1997-009, Probate files, 1887-1946 is stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Alternative Form Available
Record books, Volumes 1, 7, 8, 10, 12, and 19, 1887-1919, were microfilmed by the Genealogical Society of Utah and are available for use in the History and Genealogy reading room or through the.
Provenance
The probate files in Accession 1997-009 were transferred to the Connecticut State Library on July16. 1996.
Container List
- Probate files, 1887-1946; 50 cubic feet; 1997-009
  There is no index for these files
  - Abb. - Ban., 1887-1933 (Box 1)
  - Ban. - Bidwell, E., 1887-1933 (Box 2)
  - Bidwell, E. - Bou., 1887-1933 (Box 3)
  - Bou. - Brewer, L., 1887-1933 (Box 4)
  - Brewer, L. - Burnham, J., 1887-1933 (Box 5)
  - Burnham, J. - Clark, E., 1887-1933 (Box 6)
  - Clark, J. - Cra., 1887-1933 (Box 7)
  - Cre. - Donahue, 1887-1933 (Box 8)
  - Donovan - Fea., 1887-1933 (Box 9)
  - Fee. - For., 1887-1933 (Box 10)
  - Fos. - Gid., 1887-1933 (Box 11)
  - Gil. - Hale., 1887-1933 (Box 12)
  - Hall - Hills, A., 1887-1933 (Box 13)
  - Hills, C. - How., 1887-1933 (Box 14)
  - Hoy. - Kas., 1887-1933 (Box 15)
  - Kea. - King., 1887-1933 (Box 16)
  - Kinghorn - Lit., 1887-1933 (Box 17)
  - Liu. - Mal., 1887-1933 (Box 18)
  - Man. - Mc., 1887-1933 (Box 19)
  - Mea. - Mur., 1887-1933 (Box 20)
  - Mye. - Osb., 1887-1933 (Box 21)
  - Ost. - Pit., 1887-1933 (Box 22)
  - Piz. - Rey., 1887-1933 (Box 23)
  - Ric. - Rog., 1887-1933 (Box 24)
  - Roh. - Sho., 1887-1933 (Box 25)
  - Sic. - Steele, John, 1887-1933 (Box 26)
  - Steele, Joseph - Tho., 1887-1933 (Box 27)
  - Thr. - War., 1887-1933 (Box 28)
  - War. - Williams, 1887-1933 (Box 29)
  - Willis - Z., 1887-1933 (Box 30)
  - A. - Bea., 1934-1946 (Box 31)
  - Bec. - Brewer, E., 1934-1946 (Box 32)
  - Brewer, F. - Carr, 1934-1946 (Box 33)
  - Carro. - Conn., 1934-1946 (Box 34)
  - Conw. - Dea., 1934-1946 (Box 35)
  - Dev. - Fea., 1934-1946 (Box 36)
  - Fla. - Garv., 1934-1946 (Box 37)
  - Gary - Has., 1934-1946 (Box 38)
  - Hat. - Hot., 1934-1946 (Box 39)
  - Hou. - Kis., 1934-1946 (Box 40)
  - Kle. - Lin., 1934-1946 (Box 41)
  - Liu. - McC., 1934-1946 (Box 42)
  - McD. - Mye., 1934-1946 (Box 43)
  - N. - Pec., 1934-1946 (Box 44)
  - Ped. - Ray., 1934-1946 (Box 45)
  - Rea. - Sch., 1934-1946 (Box 46)
  - Sco. - Squ., 1934-1946 (Box 47)
  - Sta. - Thr., 1934-1946 (Box 48)
  - Tib. - Wes., 1934-1946 (Box 49)
  - Wet. - Z., 1934-1946 (Box 50)